so my parents got divorced when i was a
kid and my mom remarried my stepfather i
love my stepfather uh helped me become a
man um i just think he's a little too
humble he's a quiet guy
so i went to the united states air force
academy so i went to college thank you
very much
so after basic training and then like in
the middle of the semester they let your
parents visit for parents weekend first
time my parents they come to visit me at
the air force academy we're driving
around
i'm like hey dad let's go look at the
f-86 that's my favorite all-time fighter
plane he's been married to my mother for
10 years at this point he goes oh yes i
flew that in the venezuelan air force
what
you were a venezuelan fighter pilot he's
like jess
how was that
he goes it was fun
did you ever get shot at jess
how was that it's scary a little more
information dad
so i have been in the air force a long
time and that's what i tell audiences
because i used to tell them i'm an air
force pilot which i am and audiences
didn't know what to do with that they'd
be like they let the cubans fly the
plane
shouldn't he be in the coast guard
you don't want cubans in the coast guard
people gonna start talking
like mexicans in the border patrol
just gonna assume it's like stop right
there oh that's my cousin okay
i don't need that kind of pressure
[Applause]
been in the air force a long time this
year in june will be 27 years since i
joined
you know what i discovered we
are not considered the tough branch
[Applause]
i think it's because we don't have a
cheer right army's like hoo-ha marines
like
air force like four like we don't have a
good shoe
it's hard to motivate a room full of air
forces like 80 desk jobs you're like air
force they're like paper cuts are real
bro
we don't even have an accurate song the
air force song says nothing can stop the
us air force that is not true
they need to add some words in theirs
and nothing can stop the us air force
unless the internet is down and
[Applause]
we're not as effective at that point
we had a tough guy we had an air force
tough guy i was kind of proud of it i
don't know if you remember they made a
movie about it there was a gunman on a
train in paris years back and an air
force airman
tackled that gunman and save a bunch of
lives
yeah i was like yes baby air force got
our tough guy now we got a tough guy and
then the shirt i'm on tv with his shirt
off i'm like you gotta work out man
come on you're our first stuff guy
come on
i had to add a part to that joke
because i was doing a show in vegas
and three rows back he
stood up
i was like you're bigger than tv
so
i just want to say for the record in
case you're watching uh he has amazing
abs and eyes you can just lost in
forever he's really good with animals
and he loves walks on the beach and
he's sensitive but also strong alright
so
[Applause]
don't beat me
you